<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docs on CoreUI Icons</title>
    <link>https://icons.coreui.io/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docs on CoreUI Icons</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://icons.coreui.io/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Build tools</title>
      <link>https://icons.coreui.io/docs/getting-started/build-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icons.coreui.io/docs/getting-started/build-tools/</guid>
      <description>Tooling setup CoreUI Icons uses npm scripts for its build system. Our package.json includes convenient methods for working with the framework, including compiling code, running tests, and more.
To use our build system and run our documentation locally, you&amp;rsquo;ll need a copy of CoreUI Icons&amp;rsquo;s source files and Node. Follow these steps and you should be ready to rock:
 Download and install Node.js, which we use to manage our dependencies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI Icons</title>
      <link>https://icons.coreui.io/docs/getting-started/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icons.coreui.io/docs/getting-started/introduction/</guid>
      <description>.cd-example i { font-size: 2rem; }  Installation NPM npm install @coreui/icons@next --save Yarn yarn add @coreui/icons@next Or, you can also clone or download this repository as zip.
Usage Basic Use You can place CoreUI Icons just about anywhere using a CSS style prefix and the icon’s name. CoreUI Icons are designed to be used with inline elements ex. &amp;lt;i&amp;gt; or &amp;lt;span&amp;gt;.
Please use cil- prefix for linear icons, cib- prefix for brand icons, and cif- prefix for flag icons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI Icons for Angular</title>
      <link>https://icons.coreui.io/docs/using-coreui-icons-with/angular/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icons.coreui.io/docs/using-coreui-icons-with/angular/</guid>
      <description>Cooming Soon</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI Icons for React.js</title>
      <link>https://icons.coreui.io/docs/using-coreui-icons-with/react/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icons.coreui.io/docs/using-coreui-icons-with/react/</guid>
      <description>CIcon React component Dedicated component used to implement CoreUI Icons SVG set in React.js.
For component description visit CIcon component documentation
Installation If you already have installed CoreUI React component library plugin, then you have CIcon component already installed, otherwise install package by:
NPM npm install @coreui/icons-react --save Yarn yarn add @coreui/icons-react Icon importing There are three ways of icon importing:
passing icon name by &amp;lsquo;name&amp;rsquo; prop (recommended) - this way you import your needed icons once and pass them to $root object on &amp;lsquo;icons&amp;rsquo; key.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI Icons for Vue</title>
      <link>https://icons.coreui.io/docs/using-coreui-icons-with/vue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icons.coreui.io/docs/using-coreui-icons-with/vue/</guid>
      <description>CIcon Vue component Dedicated component used to implement CoreUI Icons SVG set in Vue.js.
Features  Can load icons in three ways:  stored globally in Vue root object, directly passed SVG tag content, source link to SVG file  Greatly reduce icons bundle size, when imported as single icons, Full functionality of &amp;lsquo;svg&amp;rsquo; html tag, Clean API  For component description visit CIcon component documentation
Installation If you already have installed CoreUI Vue component library plugin, then you have CIcon component already installed, otherwise install package by:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>